<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Truong's Website</title><link href="https://ttran0.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://ttran0.github.io/feeds/teaching-page.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://ttran0.github.io/</id><updated>2016-12-23T20:48:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>Teaching Page</title><link href="https://ttran0.github.io/teaching.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-12-23T20:48:00-08:00</published><updated>2016-12-23T20:48:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Truong Tran</name></author><id>tag:ttran0.github.io,2016-12-23:teaching.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Teaching Philosophy &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My teaching philosophy is to bring the curiosity out of students and to communicate that all students are capable of understanding mathematics. Through my experience as a lecturer, I have noticed that students are more successful when they become invested in the material. Thus, I aspire to ignite the curiosity within my students. In order to do so, I make out-of-classroom connections between course content and their future careers. As a vast majority of my students are engineers and as I teach courses in the computer science and computer engineering departments, I have the opportunity to develop a deep understanding from my colleagues of how mathematics is applied in the field of engineering. Furthermore, I strive to remain aware of trends in the mathematics and engineering fields by subscribing to newsletters, following prominent organizations in the media, and attending conferences and meet-ups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to promoting curiosity, my teaching philosophy includes the mindset that mathematics is a skill that anyone can learn  by constantly encouraging my students to learn critical and applicable concepts. My students have also learned that the understanding of these concepts is possible, regardless of natural ability, given time and practice. I also create an atmosphere of inclusion and approachability, my students feel comfortable asking questions whenever they arise. This includes during class time, office hours, if they see me on campus, and even via email.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="teaching"></category></entry></feed>